let MCQS = [{
    question: "appering to be legitmate, which of the following malicious programs is used to target banking/ payment systems to access confidential info?",
    choice1: "Trojan Horse",
    choice2: "Ransomeware",
    choice3: "Backdoor",
    choice4: "Social Engineering",
    answer: 0
},
            {
            question: "Choose the Correct Malware term that describes a controversial program designed to propagate across networks for distributing secuirty patches for vulnerabilities?",
    choice1: "keylogger",
    choice2: "Ethical worm",
    choice3: "Spyware",
    choice4: "Patch management",
    answer: 1
},
            {
            question: "What malware was in a news recently for taking down the irish health service?",
    choice1: "Ransomeware",
    choice2: "Logic bomb",
    choice3: "DDoS",
    choice4: "Port scan",
    answer: 0
},
            {
            question: "Which of the following describes a self-replicating malware that spreads by duplicating.?",
    choice1: "Worm",
    choice2: "Botnet",
    choice3: "malicious link",
    choice4: "Hybrid virus",
    answer: 0
},
            {
            question: "Once installed, which collection of software tools is used to gain remote access to and control over a computer or system?",
    choice1: "Rootkit",
    choice2: "Penetration test",
    choice3: "virus",
    choice4: "Logic bomb",
    answer: 0
},
            {
            question: "Fill in the blanks: ______ is used legitimately in free versions of applications to display advertisements while a program is running?",
    choice1: "Spyware",
    choice2: "Adware",
    choice3: "Shareware",
    choice4: "Ransomware",
    answer: 1
},
            {
               question: "Phishing, spear phishing, vishing, scareware and watering hole attacks are all types of ______.",
    choice1: "Probes",
    choice2: "Insider threats",
    choice3: "Social engineering",
    choice4: "Ransomeware",
    answer: 2
},{
               question: "Choose the term that describes the dangerous malware that takes over a victim's machine and abuses compute resources to mine digital currency and transfer it to the criminal's digital wallet.",
    choice1: "Bitcoin",
    choice2: "Cryptominer",
    choice3: "Monero",
    choice4: "Graceful degradation",
    answer: 1
},
            {
               question: "Which of the following attacks uses a botnet to overwhelm a server or other network resource with fraudulent traffic, thus triggering the system to deny access to legitimate users? ",
    choice1: "DoS",
    choice2: "DDoS",
    choice3: "IoT",
    choice4: "Command and Control",
    answer: 1
},
            {
               question: "Which of the following is not an indicator of a DoS attack?",
    choice1: "Degradation of network performance",
    choice2: "Specific website is unavailable",
    choice3: "Inability to access any website",
    choice4: "Lower than usual volume of spam email",
    answer: 3
}];